>> Brian Holt: 这是从先前版本的
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This is a little bit
abbreviated from previous versions of
我教过的雷杜克斯
Redux that I've taught.
而这就是 Redux 越来越少的原因
And the reason being for
that is Redux is kind of becoming less and
在 React 社区中不那么重要。
less important in the React community.
随着环境 API 的出现，我们不再需要它了。
With the advent of solid context API,
we don't need it as much anymore.
现在我们有了 Reducer ，我们也有很多好处，
And now that we have useReducer, we kinda
got a lot of those benefits as well,
所以我们更需要它
so we need it even less.
现在你在问我什么时候能用雷杜克斯
Now you're asking,
when would I ever use Redux?
今天的答案是我可能再也不用专业的 Redux 了
The answer today is I probably won't
ever use Redux professionally again.
我可能不会再选择再使用 Redux 了
I probably won't elect to
use Redux ever again, but
我不是说你不该来
I'm not saying that you shouldn't.
所以，如果它真的与你的精神模型有问题，或者类似的话。
So if it really jives with your mental
model of a problem or something like that.
或者我稍后会遇到一个不一样的问题
Or I might later run into
a problem that's like no, man,
我希望我能用雷杜克斯
I wish I would have used Redux.
所以我不知道
So I don't know, but
我现在的精神状态不好当我用 Redux的时候
I don't have a good mental image
right now of when I would use Redux.
所以我还会继续
So the reason why I'm still gonna
教你这是因为我想让你自己决定对吧
teach you this is because I want you
to decide that for yourself, right?
我们要穿过所有你需要知道的 Redux
We're gonna walk through all the various
pieces of Redux that you need to know
做出自己的决定
to make that decision for yourself.
另外还有很多的代码库仍然存在
And the other thing is there's still
a lot of code bases out there that still
使用 Redux ，所以您仍然需要了解它。
use Redux, and so
you still kinda need to know it.
所以我要说的是也许我会用 Redux 来
So the one thing that I would say
that maybe I would use Redux for
如果我有很多异步的事情马上就会发生
is if I had a lot of asynchronous
things going on at once.
也许我得向十种不同的 API 发出请求
Maybe I had to make a request
to ten different APIs, and
他们必须以正确的顺序回到正确的秩序
they had to be in the right order and
come back in the right order.
第一，这听起来很困难，但是
One, that sounds like
a really hard problem, but
Redux 在这种情况下会很有帮助的事情叫做萨加斯
Redux would actually be very helpful in
that scenario with something called Sagas,
我今天绝对不教你
which I'm definitely
not teaching you today.
但 Sagas 非常困难，但它们也很强大。
But Sagas are very difficult,
but they also are powerful.
我相信史蒂夫在他的高级管理课程里教他们
I believe that Steve teaches them in
his Advanced State Management course
在 FrontEndMasters上。
on FrontEndMasters.
如果你想更多了解勒杜克斯看史蒂夫的课程
So if you wanna know more about Redux,
watch Steve's course.
或者如果你想了解 React 和 Redux 的更多信息
Or if you wanna know more about React and
Redux together,
这三个版本的版本比我今天要去的还要多
version three of this course goes a little
bit further than I wanna go today.
所以今天我们要和雷德克斯同步了对吧
So today we're just gonna go
over synchronous Redux, right?
我们不会去拿那些异步的东西我们甚至会去
We're not gonna go over the asynch stuff,
we're gonna even go over thunks or
任何类似的事情
anything like that.
我们要把雷德克斯的事交给他
We're just gonna go over what Redux is.
>> Brian Holt: 那么，我们又如何与 Redux建立关系 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So again,
how did we end up with Redux?
我们没有使用上下文，所以这就更有用了。
We didn't use to have Context, so
this used to be a lot more useful.
但现在我们有了好的背景，即使是丹 - 阿布拉莫夫，
But now that we have good context, even
Dan Abramov, the creator of Redux is like,
我不再真正使用 Redux 了
I don't really use Redux anymore.
>> Brian Holt: 好，那么 Redux 是什么意思 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so what is Redux for?
如果你记得在  中我们谈过
Well, if you remember in the Intro
to React, we talked about
有时在这边有个国店是很有用的，对吧 ?
sometimes it's really useful to have
a state store on the side, right?
所以我们的主要应用和所有组件都有各自的状态
So we have our main application and
all the components have all their state,
但如果我有一个用户，对，如果我的每一项申请
but if I have a user, right,
if every piece of my application
需要从用户对象中读取，我不需要在任何地方都通过，对吗 ?
needs to read from the user object, I
don't have to pass that everywhere, right?
如果我能把它放在那边的话会很有用的
So it'd be useful if I could put
that somewhere on the side, and
这就是 Redux 真正有用的地方
that's where Redux is really useful.
它是您应用程序中状态的中央存储库，可以吗 ?
It's a central repository for
state in your application, okay?
因此，通常在 React 中，您只会调用 setState 并让 React 重新呈现，对吗 ?
So typically in React you would just call
setState and let React rerender, right?
所以如果这是更新的方式，对，我可能是用户改变了他们的电子邮件，
So if that's how something updates, right,
I have maybe the user changes their email,
我就打电话给 setState ，那就结束了，对吧 ?
I would just call setState and
that would be the end of it, right?
在雷德克斯的时候，我们引入了一个更大的圆圈来回到那个点。
With Redux, we introduced a much bigger
circle to get back to that point.
所以我在这里为您输入了它，在收件箱或输入框中输入用户类型。
So here I've kind of typed it out for
you, user types in inbox or an input box.
它会调用操作创建者来获取将操作分派给 Redux的操作。
It calls an action creator to get an
action that dispatches an action to Redux.
然后， Redux 将操作插入根减速器。
Redux then inserts the action
into the root reducer.
根减速器分派给另一个减速器
The root reducer dispatches
to a different reducer,
它会处理状态更新。
which actually handles the state update.
此减速器返回给定该操作对象的新状态。
The reducer returns a new state
given that action object.
这个新状态变成了源状态，并反馈到 React中，对吗 ?
This new state becomes the source state,
and that is fed back into React, right?
所以一方面你有八个步骤
So on one hand you have
these eight steps versus
setState，或更新挂钩，或类似的内容，对吗 ?
setState, or an update hook,
or something like that, right?
其中一个比另一个简单一些，但是
One of these is a little bit
simpler than the other, but
我会让你当个法官
I'll let you be the judge
of which one that is.
你为什么要这么做
So why would you do something like this?
一，每一步都是稳定的。
One, every step of this is testable.
这意味着你要观察你的状态
So that means you get to
observe how your state
改变这一切的每一步对吧
changes through every step of this, right?
这很有价值，对吧 ?
And that's valuable, right?
你可以说这个国家的变异
You can basically say
this mutation of state,
我可以保证，这将是正确的。
I can guarantee that given this
is going to go through correctly.
这就是 Redux 强大的原因。
And that's why Redux is powerful.
所以，让我们开始吧，开始吧。
So let's go ahead and get started on this.
所以，请转至代码编辑器并
So go to your Code Editor and
我们要去 npm install redux 和
we're going to npm install redux and
reis-redux ，它是 Redux 和 React 之间非常薄的连接器。
react-redux which is the very thin
connector between Redux and React.
因为你可能知道你可以用雷迪克斯和角
Because as you may know,
you can use Redux with Angular,
你可以用它和任何一个框架一起使用
you can use it with Ember,
it works with any framework.
您可以在没有框架的情况下使用它。
You can use it without a framework.
>> Brian Holt: 我想我想说的关于 Redux 的另一件事是
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I think the other
thing that I wanna say about Redux is
是一个很小的图书馆
it's a very small library.
实际上，您可以在大约 50 行代码中写入 Redux 。
You can actually write Redux
in about 50 lines of code.
这只是一种头脑的融化，对吧 ?
And that's just kind of mind melting,
right?
但我想说的另一件事并不意味着这很容易
But the other thing that I wanna
say is that doesn't mean it's easy,
是吗 ?
[LAUGH] right?
所以我听到有人这样说，简单但硬，对吗 ?
So I've heard someone phrase it as,
it's simple but hard, right?
而不是复杂而简单的对吧
As opposed to complex and easy, right?
我想把旧的 AngularJS 当作复杂而简单的事
I would judge old AngularJS as complex and
easy.
它有很多东西但其实很容易就能和它一起跑
It does a lot of stuff but it's actually
quite easy to get up and running with it,
但也很容易让自己陷入一个烂摊子的烂摊子里
but it's also easy to get yourself in
a really rat's nest kind of tangled mess.
我的应用程序仍在 Angular 的生产中
My applications that are still in
production in Angular are a perfect
这个例子。
example of that.
是我的错不是他们的错对吧
Which is my fault, not their fault, right?
但是我想说， Redux 非常简单，它不是很大的，
But I would say that Redux is very
simple in that it's not very big, and
没有太多的方法，但是很难理解
there's not a lot of methods to it,
but it's quite hard to understand